>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 顺便说下这个样机系统不错
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: By the way,
this prototype system, not bad at all.
它是惊人的独角兽设计，它非常强大。
It's incredibly amazingly unicorn design,
it's very powerful.
这只是一个不同的设计模式。
It's just a different design
pattern than classes.
这是一个不同的设计模式，叫做代表团。
It's a different design pattern
which is called delegation.
顺便说下我没做这个词
Now, I didn't make up this term,
by the way.
我一直在研究原型系统，以及这些东西是如何长时间工作的。
I've been studying the prototype system
and how these things work for a long time.
我没组成代表团，我是理解的，我破产了
I didn't make up delegation,
what I did was I understood, I broke
所有关于 JavaScript 和链接的作品都不复制
down all the pieces of how JavaScript
works and the linkages and it's not copy.
我建立了这个系统的精神模型
And I built up this mental
model of the system and
然后有一天我在网上冲浪去尝试研究
then one day, I was just surfing on
the internet trying to research stuff and
我穿过一个名叫 " 代表团" 的维基百科
I ran across a Wikipedia
page called Delegation, and
我开始阅读这个设计模式，叫做 " 代表团" 。
I started reading about this
design pattern called Delegation.
我就像是，这听起来真的，真的很熟悉。
And I was like, that sounds really,
really, really familiar.
灯泡的瞬间，就是 JavaScript 的内容。
The light bulb moment,
that's what JavaScript is.
我没有发明这个词
I didn't invent the term.
委派或行为委托。
Delegation or behavior delegation.
我刚给苹果打了个苹果
I just called an apple an apple.
这就是 JavaScript 的系统。
That's what JavaScript's system is.
它的原型系统是一个代表团系统，而不是一个类系统。
Its prototype system is a delegation
system, not a class system.
如果您将委派和类视为不同的设计模式。
If you think about delegation and
classes as different design pattern.
不是说一个是坏，另一个是好的，
Rather than saying one is bad and
the other is good,
我不是说上课不好
I'm not saying that classes are bad.
我只是说他们在一个设计成一个代表团的系统里不合适
I'm just saying they don't fit in a system
that was designed to be a delegation
系统。
system.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们一直在努力让它适应
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And
we've been trying to make it fit and
我们一直试图把它塞进它的胶带里
we keep trying to shove it in there and
duct tape it to make it fit.
也许更有效的方法是说，嘿，系统，你是怎么设计的 ?
And maybe the more effective thing is to
say, hey, system, how are you designed?
如果我用你实际工作的方式，我能做些什么神奇的事情呢 ?
What amazing things can I do with you if
I use the way that you actually work?
这个想法对我来说并不是独一无二的。
This thought is not unique to me.
但有人观察到，如果你比较一个原型系统，
But it has been observed that,
if you're comparing a prototypal system,
一个委托系统到一个类系统，这个原型系统其实是，
a delegation system, to a class system,
that the prototypal system is actually
比一个阶级系统更强大
significantly more powerful
than a class system.
这就是为什么，如果原型系统是一个超级集合
And here's why, it is as if the prototypal
system is sort of the super set and
类系统为子集。
the class system is a subset.
这就是为什么因为你可以
And here's why,
because you can implement a class
在原型语言中的系统，但不能执行逆向操作。
system inside of a prototypal language,
but you cannot do the reverse.
不能以面向类的语言实现原型系统。
You cannot implement a prototype
system in a class-oriented language.
所以我们选择用这个惊人的强大的系统
So we chose to take this amazingly
powerful system and use it in
一个非常特别的方法，这甚至不是特别好的这个系统的使用。
one very specific way that's not even
a particularly good usage of the system.
然后我们花了二十年的时间来敲敲我们的头。
And then we spent 20
years banging our heads.
这工作为什么不像其他语言一样呢 ?
Why doesn't this work like
it does in other languages?
我的反应是你做了错误的模式
My response is because you're
doing the wrong pattern.
你可以上课
You can do classes.
你们中的一些人必须去做一些课程因为你工作的框架
And some of you have to do classes because
you work with frameworks that make that
你的选择
choice for you.
但我不希望你从这个讨论中走出来
But what I don't want you to do is walk
away from this discussion thinking well,
这是我唯一的选择
it's my only option.
这不是你唯一的选择
It's not your only option.
这个系统存在，而且有很多未开发的潜力。
This system exists, and there's so
much untapped potential.
我想在我们最后的时候在这个单位
And what I wanna dig into in our
final time together in this unit,
我想知道的是如果我们把我们的
what I wanna dig into is, what can we
do with delegation if we set aside our
这些都是最重要的设计模式吗
preconceptions that classes are the only
design pattern that matters?